classicsonline.com 2012-10-02

# ClassicsOnline Privacy Policy

Our business has been built on the trust and confidence our customers place in us. We respect our customers' privacy and we are committed to safeguarding and keeping confidential any information relating to them.

In addition to our duty of confidentiality to customers, we shall at all times fully observe the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance ("the Ordinance") of the Hong Kong SAR in collecting, maintaining and using the personal data of customers.

Customers' personal data are classified as confidential and can only be disclosed by us where permitted by the Ordinance or if we are otherwise legally compelled to do so.

We only collect personal information to assist us in providing you with services as well as information on services offered by us.

We may collect personal information from you in a number of ways including: (a) directly from you, such as when you enter your personal details on our website (for example during registration or application for our services), when you provide information by phone or in documents such as an application form; (b) from our affiliated companies; (c) from your representatives; (d) from publicly available sources of information; (e) from credit-reporting and fraud-checking agencies and credit providers for credit-related purposes such as credit worthiness, credit rating, credit provision and financing; (f) from our own records of your dealings with us; or (g) when legally required to do so.

The personal information we collect from you includes your Username, Password, E-mail and Postal address. Credit card information we collect from you will go directly to our Bank and no personnel of Naxos Digital Services will have access to these data.

Your personal information may be used by us: (a) to identify you; (b) in providing service to you and the administration and management of those services; (c) to provide you with information on services offered by us; (d) in undertaking risk assessment and management; or (e) in gathering data necessary for our organisation's functions including dealings with credit reporting agencies, financial institutions including our own bankers, service providers, our professional advisers, including our accountants, auditors and lawyers, insurers and industry groups having a legitimate reason to receive such information.

We do not provide any personal information provided by you to any third parties other than to our affiliated companies or where required by law or as set out in this Privacy Policy. We will not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. We may provide aggregate statistics on users of our website to third parties such as advertisers, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. We co-operate with law enforcement agencies.

If you provide us with personally identifiable information, you may receive emails or direct marketing containing promotional material from us. You may receive e-mails from us including information on the areas of interest you have indicated or other types of news and information on our products and/or services. If you do not want to receive them, please contact us. You may be asked to indicate your preference for receiving promotional material, when submitting information to us.

Cookies that are used in any part of our website will not be utilised for collecting personally identifiable information and will only be used for internal management purposes.

We may employ other companies or individuals to provide certain services such as analysing customer lists, providing marketing assistance or consulting services. These third parties may have access to information needed to perform their function but can not use that information for other purposes.

All reasonable steps are taken to correct information held where the information is not accurate, up-to-date and complete.

All reasonable steps are taken to ensure that all information is treated confidentially, kept secure and protected against unauthorised use and is maintained only for the purpose for which it is intended. Your e-mail address will not be distributed to any third party.

The copyright and related rights in all material sent to you belong to Naxos Digital Services Ltd. Naxos Digital Services Ltd. and are for personal use only. No other uses are permitted without the prior permission of Naxos Digital Services Ltd.

For further information on our Privacy Policy please contact our Privacy Officer by sending a message to customer service.

If any of the personal information you have submitted changes, please update that information by clicking into the Manage Account and make the necessary changes.

You have the right to access your personal information and requests for information about our Privacy Policy are welcomed. Request for access to data or correction of data or for information regarding policies and practices and data held should be addressed to:

**Customer Service**  
**Naxos Digital Services Limited**  
Level 11, Cyberport 1,  
100 Cyberport Road  
Hong Kong 

Telephone: (852) 2760-7818 (non toll-free)  
Fax: (852) 2760-1962 (non toll-free)  
Email: Customer Service
